http://eurotas.org/data-protection-privacy-policy-cookie-policy

Home » DATA PROTECTION – Privacy Policy, Cookie Policy
DATA PROTECTION – Privacy Policy, Cookie Policy
Privacy Policy Privacy Policy
European Transpersonal Association (collectively, “EUROTAS”, “we”, “us”, and “our”) respect your privacy. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy (“this Policy”). This Policy applies to EUROTAS website and services that display or provide links to this Policy.
This Policy describes how EUROTAS processes your personal data, but it may not address all possible data processing scenarios. EUROTAS may inform you of service-specific data collection through supplementary policies or notices provided before collection.
How We Collect & Use Your Personal Data
Personal data means any data that, either on its own or jointly with other data, can be used to identify a natural person. You directly provide us with such data when you use our websites, or services, or interact with us by, for example, contacting us for support. We may also obtain data by recording how you interact with our websites or services. For example, we may use technologies like cookies or receive use data from software running on your device. The personal data we collect includes name, gender, enterprise name, job position, postal and email addresses, phone number, etc., depending on how you interact with EUROTAS, for example, the website you visit or the services that you use. We also collect the information you provide to us and the content of messages you send us, such as the query information you provide, or the questions or information you provide for customer service support.
Contacting us
Should you have a particular query or feedback, you may contact us through the contact forms available on our website. In such context, we may process your Personal Data for the purposes of handling and providing an answer to your query or request or to follow up on your feedback. In this case, we will process all Personal Data provided by you in this respect for the purposes of handling and providing an answer to your query or request.
The table below describes the types of data we process for these purposes, where we get your data from, the ground we rely on to carry out the processing, and who we may share your data with.
Processed data categories
Source of data
Ground for processing
Recipients of data
First Name, Last Name, Company, Job Title, Country, Address, Work Phone, Fax, Home Phone, Email Address, Experience and other job and qualification related information
Directly from you through the forms
Ad hoc consent obtained through the contact form
EUROTAS
IT service provider
The purposes of the processing of data are set out in Article 2 of our Constitution (https://eurotas.org/eurotas-constitution/).
Your rights
GDPR grants specific rights, summarized below, which you can exercise free of charge, subject to statutory exceptions. These rights may be limited, for example if fulfilling your request would reveal Personal Data about another person, or if you ask us to delete information which we are required by law to keep or have compelling legitimate interests in keeping. To exercise any of your rights, you can file a request here  mail@eurotas.org.
Should you have unresolved concerns, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a Supervisory Authority where you live or where you believe a breach may have occurred. We encourage you to come to us in the first instance but, to the extent that this right applies to you, you are entitled to complain directly to the relevant Supervisory Authority.
2.1. Right to withdraw consent
Wherever we rely on your consent, you will be able to withdraw that consent at any time you choose and at your own initiative by contacting us here mail@eurotas.org. The withdrawal of your consent will not affect the lawfulness of the collection and processing of your data based on your consent up until the moment where you withdraw your consent. Please note that we may have other legal grounds for processing your data for other purposes, such as those set out in this Privacy Policy.
2.2. Right to access and rectify your data
You have the right to access, review, and rectify your Personal Data. You may be entitled to ask us for a copy of your information, to review or correct it if you wish to rectify any information like your name, email address and/or any other preferences, you can easily do so by contacting us here mail@eurotas.org. You may also request a copy of the Personal Data processed as described in this Privacy Policy.
2.3. Right to erasure
In accordance with GDPR, you have the right to erasure of your Personal Data processed by us as described in this Privacy Policy in case it is no longer needed for the purposes for which the Personal Data was initially collected or processed or in the event you have withdrawn your consent or objected to processing as described in this Privacy Policy and no other legal ground for processing applies. Should you wish to have your Personal Data erased, please file a request here mail@eurotas.org.
2.4. Right to restriction of processing
Under certain circumstances described in GDPR, you may ask us to restrict the processing of your Personal Data. This is for example the case when you contest the accuracy of your Personal Data. In such event, we will restrict the processing until we can verify the accuracy of your data.
2.5. Right to object to processing
Under certain circumstances described in GDPR, you may object to the processing of your Personal Data, including where your Personal Data is processed for direct marketing purposes.
2.6. Right to data portability
Where you have provided your data directly to us and where the processing is carried out by automated means and based on your consent or the performance of a contract between you and us, you have the right to receive the Personal Data processed about you in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format, and to transmit this data to another service provider.
Security measures
Appropriate technical and organizational measures are implemented in order to ensure an appropriate level of security of your Personal Data, including but not limited to encryption techniques, physical and IT system access controls, obligations of confidentiality, etc.
In the event Personal Data is compromised as a result of a Personal Data Breach we will make the necessary notifications, as required under applicable laws.
How is your Personal Data shared with Third Parties?
We only share or disclose information as described herein, including with Third Parties.
Your Personal Data will also be shared with government authorities and/or law enforcement officials if required for the purposes above, if mandated by law or if required for the legal protection of the Controller(s) legitimate interests in compliance with applicable laws.
International Data Transfers
If you are in the European Economic Area (EEA), the data that we collect from you as described in this policy may be transferred to and stored at a destination outside the EEA. Countries outside the EEA may not have laws which provide the same level of protection to your Personal Data as laws within the EEA. Where this is the case we will put in place appropriate safeguards to ensure that such transfers comply with GDPR, either by putting in place Standard Contractual Clauses approved by the European Commission as ensuring an adequate protection or by ensuring that the transfer is done to an organisation that complies with Privacy Shield in case the transfer is made to the United States of America.
In case you wish to obtain more details about our data transfer safeguards and the mechanisms in place, you may contact us at mail@eurotas.org.
How long will we keep your Personal Data?
We retain your Personal Data for as long as is required to fulfil the activities set out in this Privacy Policy, for as long as otherwise communicated to you or for as long as is permitted by applicable law. For example, we may retain your Personal Data if it is reasonably necessary to comply with any legal obligations, meet any regulatory requirements, resolve any disputes or litigation, or as otherwise needed to enforce this Policy and prevent fraud and abuse.
To determine the appropriate retention period for the information we collect from you, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the Personal Data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of the data, the purposes for which we process the Personal Data, and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.
Does this Privacy Policy apply to Third Party websites?
If you click on a link to a Third-Party website, you will be taken to a website we do not control and our Privacy Policy will no longer be in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website is subject to the terms of use and privacy and other policies of such Third-Party website. Read the privacy policies of other websites carefully. We are not responsible or liable for the information or content on such Third-Party websites.
What happens if we make modifications to this Policy?
We reserve the right to modify and update this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will bring these changes to your attention should they be indicative of a fundamental change to the processing or be relevant to the nature of the processing or be relevant to you and impact your data protection rights.
How to contact us?
Questions, comments, remarks, requests or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy are welcome and should be addressed to: mail@eurotas.org or A-1090, Vienna, Porzellangasse 56/2/10.
Cookie Policy Cookie Policy
When you visit this website, we place small files called cookies on your computer or mobile device.
What are cookies?
A cookie is a small text file that a website saves on your computer or mobile device when you visit the site. It enables the website to remember your actions and preferences (such as login, language, font size and other display preferences) over a period of time, so you don’t have to keep re-entering them whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another.
Other cookies, from third parties, could also be used to track you when you navigate to other sites that also use services from these third parties.
How do we use cookies?
Our pages use “session” cookies to remember for example your language choices and display preferences (such as contrast colour settings or font size). These cookies are deleted from your computer when you close your browser.
We also use a limited number of persistent cookies. These remain stored on your computer until you delete them, or until they expire after, usually after a short period of time going up to 1 year
The persistent cookies contain the following information:
the state (collapsed or expanded) of some menus and widgets
the selected tab in the widgets
Enabling these cookies is not strictly necessary for the main functions of the website to work, but it will provide you with a better browsing experience. However, you can delete or block these cookies at any time.
The cookie-related information is not used to identify you personally and the pattern data is fully under our control. These cookies are not used for any purpose other than those described here.
The cookies used are the following:
Necessary (3) – Necessary cookies help make a website usable by enabling basic functions like page navigation and access to secure areas of the website. The website cannot function properly without these cookies.
COOKIE NAME
PROVIDER
PURPOSE
EXPIRY
TYPE
[SessionID#27]
paypal.com
Unclassified
1 day
HTTP
akavpau_ppsd
paypal.com
This cookie is provided by Paypal. The cookie is used in context with transaction son the website – The cookie is necessary for secure transactions.
Session
HTTP
PYPF
paypalobjects.com
This cookie is necessary for the PayPal login -function on the website.
27 days
HTTP
Preferences (1) – Preference cookies enable a website to remember information that changes the way the website behaves or looks, like your preferred language or the region that you are in.
COOKIE NAME
PROVIDER
PURPOSE
EXPIRY
TYPE
_AVESTA_ENVIRONMENT
mc.us9.list-manage.com
The cookie is set when the user subscribes to an email service from MailCh imp.
Session
HTTP
Marketing (18) – Marketing cookies are used to track visitors across websites. The intention is to display ads that are relevant and engaging for the individual user and thereby more valuable for publishers and third party advertisers.
COOKIE NAME
PROVIDER
PURPOSE
EXPIRY
TYPE
__widgetsettings
twitter.com
Unclassified
Persistent
HTML
_awl
eurotas.org
Collects data on visitors’ preferences and behaviour on the website – This information is used make content and advertisement more relevant to the specific visitor
3 years
HTTP
_pinterest_cm
pinterest.com
Used by Pinterest to track the u sage of services.
1 year
HTTP
01AI
abmr.net
Used for gathering technical information regarding the user’s browser, operating system, IP address and screen resolution as well as the user’s navigation on the website.
1 year
HTTP
GPS
youtube.com
Registers a unique ID on mobile devices to enable tracking based on geographical GPS location.
1 day
HTTP
IDE
doubleclick.net
Used by Google DoubleClick to register an d report the website user’s actions after viewing or clicking one of the advertiser’s ads with the purpose of measuring the efficacy of an ad and to present targeted ads to the user.
1 year
HTTP
local_storage_support_test
twitter.com
The cookie is used in context with the local-storage function in the browser. This function allows the website to load faster by pre-loading certain procedures.
Persistent
HTML
NID
google.com
Registers a unique ID that identifies a returning user’s device. The ID is used for targeted ads.
6 months
HTTP
PREF
youtube.com
Registers a unique ID that is used by Google to keep statistics of how the visitor uses YouTube videos across different websites.
8 months
HTTP
test_cookie
doubleclick.net
Used to check if the user’s browser supports cookies.
1 day
HTTP
VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE
youtube.com
Tries to estimate the users’ bandwidth on pages with integrated YouTube videos.
179 days
HTTP
YSC
youtube.com
Registers a unique ID to keep statistics of what videos from YouTube the user has seen.
Session
HTTP
yt-remote-cast-installed
youtube.com
Stores the user’s video player preferences using embedded YouTube video.
Session
HTML
yt-remote-connected-devices
youtube.com
Stores the user’s video player preferences using embedded YouTube video.
Persistent
HTML
yt-remote-device-id
youtube.com
Stores the user’s video player preferences using embedded YouTube video.
Persistent
HTML
yt-remote-fast-check-period
youtube.com
Stores the user’s video player preferences using embedded YouTube video.
Session
HTML
yt-remote-session-app
youtube.com
Stores the user’s video player preferences using embedded YouTube video.
Session
HTML
yt-remote-session-name
youtube.com
Stores the user’s video player preferences using embedded YouTube video.
Session
HTML
Private data
The cookie-related information is not used to identify you personally and the data collected on your browsing behaviour on our website is kept in fully secure conditions. These cookies are not used for any purpose other than those described here.
How to control cookies
You can control and/or delete cookies as you wish – for details, see aboutcookies.org. You can delete all cookies that are already on your computer and you can set most browsers to prevent them from being placed. If you do this, however, you may have to manually adjust some preferences every time you visit a site and some services and functionalities may not work.
You can easily accept or reject the cookies on this site by choosing one of the following links: I accept cookies / I refuse cookies(*).
(*) You can only refuse persistent cookies that are not strictly necessary. Some cookies are needed, as they enable us to provide certain features, such as remembering your cookies control choice. Other cookies help us collect reliable site usage information through WebTrend Analytics, which allows us to measure how well the site meets the needs of its users and to make any necessary improvements.
2019-12-04
Oleg
Monthly Joke
Fly in my Soup
November 1, 2020
Monthly Joke – Septembre
October 2, 2020
Monthly Joke August 2020
January 15, 2020
Moments we’ve spent together at the First Milan Transpersonal Festival
August 17, 2015
Eurotas Board
July 30, 2012
Newsletters 1999-2008
July 26, 1999
Fly in my Soup
November 1, 2020
Fly in my Soup
August 30, 2020
cabinetpsihoterapie.ro: Good post. I learn something new and challenging on blogs I...
Linda Truax: Hello, our mutual friend Bonnie Greenwell Ph.D. recommended...
Eliza Megan: Hi, I hope you are safe in this pandemic situation by avoidi...
© 2004-2020 - Eurotas.org - The European Transpersonal Association
/
Tel: +371 29528591
/
Email: mail[at]eurotas.org
/ Site Map /
Create by Legco-IT
Translate »
This website uses cookies to provide you with the best browsing experience.Find out more or adjust your settings.
Accept
Change cookie settings
Close GDPR Cookie Settings
Privacy Policy
Strictly Necessary Cookies
Powered by  GDPR Cookie Compliance
Privacy Policy
European Transpersonal Association (collectively, "EUROTAS", "we", "us", and "our") respect your privacy. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy ("this Policy"). This Policy applies to EUROTAS website and services that display or provide links to this Policy.
This Policy describes how EUROTAS processes your personal data, but it may not address all possible data processing scenarios. EUROTAS may inform you of service-specific data collection through supplementary policies or notices provided before collection.
Download Privacy Policy...
Strictly Necessary Cookies
Strictly Necessary Cookie should be enabled at all times so that we can save your preferences for cookie settings.
Reed Cookie policy
Enable or Disable Cookies
If you disable this cookie, we will not be able to save your preferences. This means that every time you visit this website you will need to enable or disable cookies again.
Enable All
Save Settings
